Guide to the Gay Men's Health Crisis records
The New York Public Library. Manuscripts and Archives Division.
- Series VII. Education Department, 1982-1998, n.d.; 76.75 boxes
  - VII. G. Topical Files, 1986-1995; 8 boxes
    - New York City Department of Health, 1992-1995 (Box 225, Folder 6)
    - New York City Gay and Lesbian Anti-violence Project, 1990 (Box 225, Folder 7)
    - New York City Gay and Lesbian organizations, 1987 (Box 225, Folder 8)
    - New York State Department of Health, 1992-1993 (Box 225, Folder 9)
    - Noche de Ronda, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 10)
    - Outreach training, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 11)
    - People of Color Against AIDS Network, 1991, 1994 (Box 225, Folder 12)
    - People of Color
      - Resources
        - 1990-1993 (Box 225, Folder 13-14)
        - 1994 (Box 226, Folder 1)
      - Survey, 1988 (Box 226, Folder 2)
    - Porn theater outreach, 1989 (Box 226, Folder 3)
    - Posters, 1990-1991 (Box 226, Folder 4)
    - Project PYRAMID, 1988 (Box 226, Folder 5)
    - Reinforcement/Relapse Prevention program development, 1989-1990 (Box 226, Folder 6)
    - Safer Sex Forum, 1986-1989 (Box 226, Folder 7-11)
    - San Antonio AIDS Foundation, 1990? (Box 226, Folder 12)
    - San Francisco AIDS Foundation, 1990 (Box 226, Folder 13)
    - Secondary Prevention Campaign, 1991-1993 (Box 226, Folder 14-15)
    - Sex clubs, 1990, 1995 (Box 226, Folder 16)
    - Sex, Dating & Intimacy, 1988-1991 (Box 226, Folder 17)
    - Think About It
      - 1990 (Box 226, Folder 18)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 227, Folder 1-2)
    - T-shirts, 1991-1992 (Box 227, Folder 3)
    - Tucson AIDS Project, 1990 (Box 227, Folder 4)
    - U Can Do it All, 1991 (Box 227, Folder 5)
    - Understanding Safer Sex, 1991-1992, 1995 (Box 227, Folder 6)
    - Upper Manhattan Task Force on AIDS, 1989-1991 (Box 227, Folder 7-9)
    - Voices of Color Against AIDS and for Life, 1990 (Box 227, Folder 10)
    - Volunteer positions, 1992 (Box 227, Folder 11)
    - Whitman-Walker Clinic, 1990? (Box 227, Folder 12)
    - Work plans, 1992-1993 (Box 227, Folder 13)
    - Young Adults Program
      - General
        - 1989-1993 (Box 227, Folder 14-16)
        - 1994-1995 (Box 228, Folder 1-3)
      - Resources, 1993 (Box 228, Folder 4)
  - VII. H. Treatment, Education and Advocacy, 1987-1993, n.d.; 1 box
    The Treatment Education and Advocacy division of the Education Department was created in 1993 to provide up-to-date information on current and experimental HIV/AIDS therapies to the general public. The material that was transferred from this department consists of historical files that pre-date the establishment of this unit.
    The bulk of this material is correspondence with public health, university, government, and research organizations regarding Treatment Issues, TEA's advocacy work, the participation of employees of the division in conferences and workshops on HIV/AIDS, and other topics.
    - Budget, 1991-1992 (Box 228, Folder 5)
    - Calendars, 1987-1988 (Box 228, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence
      - 1986-1989 (Box 228, Folder 7-10)
      - 1990-1993, n.d. (Box 229, Folder 1)
    - Hotline meeting minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 229, Folder 2)
    - Monthly reports, 1988-1992 (Box 229, Folder 3-4)
    - New York City Department of Health, 1991 (Box 229, Folder 5)
    - Notes, 1987-1991 (Box 229, Folder 6-7)
    - Treatment Issues survey, undated (Box 229, Folder 8)
- Series VIII. Evaluation Research Department, 1989-1999, n.d.; 87 boxes
  The Evaluation Research Department was officially established in 1993 with the consolidation of program evaluation and research service staff into one unit. Members of the department conducted quality assurance audits on GMHC programs; assisted other departments in their work, such as the effective development of ad campaigns and brochures; and conducted studies with other agencies and institutions. These collaborations included the Linkage Project, where GMHC and the Jewish Board of Family and Child Services worked to assign mental health professionals to PWAs; and in the development of the Deaf AIDS Project, where GMHC consulted with staff from the New York Society for the Deaf. In conjunction with the Research Ethics Committee (formally the Institutional Review Board until 1996), the department evaluated internal and external project proposals from researchers interested in conducting studies at GMHC.
  This series contains memoranda, project proposals, questionnaires, surveys, interview transcripts, reports, and grant applications. The series is divided into three subseries: Administrative Files, Research Materials, and Topical Files. Audiovisual materials associate with these records can be found in Series XVI.B.4.
  - VIII. A. Administrative Files, 1989-1999, n.d.; 17 boxes
    This subseries contains the Administrative Files of the Evaluation Research Department, maintained by the directors and assistant directors of the department, and proposals submitted to the Research Ethics Committee. Included in this subseries are audits of GMHC programs, development and feedback on research studies and client programs such as the Deaf AIDS Project (DAP), Gay Men of African Descent (GMAD), House of Latex (HOL) and Substance Use Counseling and Education (SUCE). Also included are applications for state and city funding that provide an overview of the department's projects and activities.
    - VIII. A. 1. Assistant Director Files, 1991-1999
      - Project proposals received
        - B-Cam, 1993-1999 (Box 229, Folder 9-17)
        - Can-Fo, 1993-1997 (Box 230, Folder 1-16)
        - Fr-H, 1993-1998 (Box 231, Folder 1-14)
        - J-Man, 1993-1998 (Box 232, Folder 1-18)
        - Mar-Mo, 1993-1998 (Box 233, Folder 1-9)
        - Mu-Rab, 1991-1998 (Box 234, Folder 1-13)
        - Ran-Stern, J, 1993-1997 (Box 235, Folder 1-12)
        - Stern, L-Wh, 1993-1997 (Box 236, Folder 1-10)
        - Wright, 1995 (Box 237, Folder 1)
    - VIII. A. 2. Director Files, 1989-1999, n.d.
      - Article 17, 1996 (Box 237, Folder 2)
      - Ball survey, 1995-1996 (Box 237, Folder 3)
      - Beaver College Collaboration, 1996-1997 (Box 237, Folder 4)
      - Board of Directors Board Program Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 237, Folder 5)
      - Budget, 1998 (Box 237, Folder 6)
      - Center for AIDS Prevention Studies, 1997 (Box 237, Folder 7)
      - Client satisfaction focus groups, 1996-1997 (Box 237, Folder 8)
      - Community Outreach presentation, undated (Box 237, Folder 9)
      - Contract spending reports, 1997 (Box 237, Folder 10)
      - Cultural competence, 1996 (Box 237, Folder 11)
      - Deaf AIDS Project
        - American Public Health Association Annual Meeting, 1996 (Box 237, Folder 12)
        - Minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 237, Folder 13)
        - Project proposal, 1995 (Box 238, Folder 1)
        - Questionnaires, 1995 (Box 238, Folder 2)
        - Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 238, Folder 3)
        - Roth, Jackie, 1995 (Box 238, Folder 4)
        - What is AIDS?, 1995 (Box 238, Folder 5)
      - Department strategic plan, 1994-1996 (Box 238, Folder 6)
      - Effectiveness research study, 1997 (Box 238, Folder 7)
      - Epidemiology presentation, 1995 (Box 238, Folder 8)
      - ERgo, 1996-1997 (Box 238, Folder 9)
      - Evaluation Research Scientific Action Group, 1994-1997 (Box 238, Folder 10)
      - Examining Clients Interest in an AIDS Video, 1994 (Box 238, Folder 11)
      - Gay Men of African Descent, 1993-1994 (Box 238, Folder 12)
      - Grant Support Committee, 1994-1997 (Box 238, Folder 13)
      - Health Services Improvement Fund
        - Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 238, Folder 14)
        - Reports, 1993 (Box 238, Folder 15)
      - HIV testing evaluations, 1995-1996 (Box 239, Folder 1)
      - Hotline
        - Evaluations, 1989-1991, 1995-1996 (Box 239, Folder 2-5)
        - Reports and tallies, 1993-1995 (Box 239, Folder 6)
        - System activity reports, 1995-1996 (Box 239, Folder 7-8)
      - House of Latex, 1993-1996 (Box 240, Folder 1)
      - Hustler Network Conference, 1993 (Box 240, Folder 2)
      - Informational and Support Network Project proposal, 1993-1994 (Box 240, Folder 3)
      - Management team, 1995-1997 (Box 240, Folder 4-5)
      - Men of Color, 1992-1995 (Box 240, Folder 6)
      - Multiculturalism, undated (Box 240, Folder 7)
      - National Development and Research Institutes, Inc., 1995 (Box 240, Folder 8)
      - National Library of Medicine proposal, 1995 (Box 241, Folder 1)
      - New York City Department of Health
        - HIV prevention proposals, 1997-1998 (Box 241, Folder 2)
        - Request for funding proposal, 1997-1999 (Box 241, Folder 3)
      - New York State
        - AIDS Institute
          - Continuation of Comprehensive Medicaid Case Management application, 1996 (Box 241, Folder 4)
          - Continued Funding applications, 1995-1997 (Box 241, Folder 5-7)
          - HIV Counseling, Testing and Prevention Initiative, 1995 (Box 241, Folder 8)
          - Objectives, 1995 (Box 241, Folder 9)
        - Department of Health application for Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program funds, 1995-1996 (Box 242, Folder 1)
      - Oral Sex and HIV Negative Young Gay/Bisexual Men
        - Brochures, 1996 (Box 242, Folder 2)
        - Project proposal, 1997 (Box 242, Folder 3)
      - Organizational charts, 1994-1996 (Box 242, Folder 4)
      - Performance evaluation guidelines, 1992-1994 (Box 242, Folder 5)
      - Personnel
        - Bratholt, Kevin, 1991-1996 (Box 242, Folder 6)
        - Kaplan, Jennifer, 1994-1997 (Box 242, Folder 7)
        - Kaplan, L., 1995-1996 (Box 242, Folder 8)
        - Kosciw, Joseph, 1994-1996 (Box 242, Folder 9)
      - Planning documents, 1994 (Box 242, Folder 10)
      - Positive testimonials campaign, 1996 (Box 242, Folder 11)
      - Practical Sampling workshop, 1995 (Box 242, Folder 12)
      - Presentations, 1996 (Box 242, Folder 13)
      - Prevention Planning Group, 1995 (Box 242, Folder 14)
      - Program
        - Audits, 1994-1995 (Box 242, Folder 15)
        - Summaries, 1994 (Box 242, Folder 16)
      - Project STAGS, 1997 (Box 243, Folder 1)
      - Project summary, 1994 (Box 243, Folder 2)
      - Protease inhibitor focus group, 1997 (Box 243, Folder 3)
      - Publications Committee, 1992, 1995-1996 (Box 243, Folder 4)
      - Quality assurance, 1992-1997 (Box 243, Folder 5)
      - Quality improvement project, 1993-1994 (Box 243, Folder 6)
      - Recovery Readiness project, 1993-1994 (Box 243, Folder 7)
      - Recruitment and Retention Committee, 1996 (Box 243, Folder 8)
      - Roper study, 1991, 1997 (Box 243, Folder 9)
      - Ryan White CARE Act grants, 1993 (Box 243, Folder 10)
      - Secondary Prevention video, 1993 (Box 243, Folder 11)
      - Service Access Committee, 1994 (Box 243, Folder 12)
      - Sex and Alcohol study, 1993 (Box 243, Folder 13)
      - Spanish Work Group committee, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 1)
      - Special requests, 1993-1994 (Box 244, Folder 2)
      - Staff meetings, 1996-1997 (Box 244, Folder 3-4)
      - Strategic planning surveys, undated (Box 244, Folder 5)
      - Substance Abuse Service Expansion Group, 1994 (Box 244, Folder 6)
      - Substance Abuse questionnaire, undated (Box 244, Folder 7)
      - SUCE
        - Background literature, 1994, n.d. (Box 244, Folder 8)
        - Curriculum specification, undated (Box 244, Folder 9)
        - Evaluation forms, undated (Box 244, Folder 10)
        - Group notes, 1995-1996 (Box 244, Folder 11)
        - New York State AIDS Institute contract, 1995-1997 (Box 244, Folder 12-13)
        - Process evaluation, 1995-1996 (Box 244, Folder 14)
        - Program review, 1995-1996 (Box 245, Folder 1)
        - Project proposal, 1996-1997 (Box 245, Folder 2)
      - Technical assistance, 1991-1992, 1996 (Box 245, Folder 3)
      - Tuberculosis
        - Client screening, undated (Box 245, Folder 4)
        - Educational materials, 1994 (Box 245, Folder 5)
        - Equipment and materials, 1994 (Box 245, Folder 6)
        - Evaluation, 1993-1994 (Box 245, Folder 7)
        - Prevention proposal, 1993 (Box 245, Folder 8)
        - Staff screening and training, 1994 (Box 245, Folder 9)
        - Volunteers, 1993-1994 (Box 245, Folder 10)
      - Volunteers, 1989-1991, 1996 (Box 245, Folder 11)
      - Women and HIV, 1994 (Box 246, Folder 1)
      - Women's Access Study, 1994 (Box 246, Folder 2-3)
      - Youth Study
        - Analysis reports, 1993-1994 (Box 246, Folder 4)
        - Coding, undated (Box 246, Folder 5)
        - Human subjects, 1993 (Box 246, Folder 6)
        - Women, 1995 (Box 246, Folder 7)
    - VIII. A. 3. Research Ethics Committee, 1993-1999
      - Agenda and minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 246, Folder 8)
      - Assurance agreement, 1995 (Box 246, Folder 9)
      - Inquiries
        - 1993-1994 (Box 246, Folder 10)
        - 1995-1999 (Box 247, Folder 1-5)
  - VIII. B. Research Materials, 1990-1997, n.d.; 69 boxes
    The Research Materials are arranged alphabetically by study and consist of surveys, questionnaires and typed transcripts of interviews. Information was gathered from participants by volunteers and department staff who spoke to participants either in person or over the phone. Some studies were used to evaluate the effectiveness of GMHC programs, such as the Keep It Up and Hotline studies, while others, Deaf AIDS Project Brochure Focus Group, were used to assist other departments to disseminate information more effectively to their targeted audience. Additional materials related to surveys can be found in the Education Department records, Series VII.F.
    - AIDS Professional Education Program
      - Questionnaires
        - Facilitator, undated (Box 247, Folder 6)
        - Pre-training
          - Undated (Box 247, Folder 7-8)
          - Undated (Box 248, Folder 1)
        - Post-training (Box 248, Folder 2)
    - Ball Survey
      - Background questionnaires, undated (Box 248, Folder 3)
      - Interviews
        - 1995 (Box 248, Folder 4-8)
      - Interview data, 1996 (Box 249, Folder 1-2)
    - Bridges Client Satisfaction survey, undated (Box 249, Folder 3)
    - Child Life Survey
      - 1997 (Box 249, Folder 4-6)
      - 1997 (Box 250-252)
      - 1997 (Box 253, Folder 1)
    - Client Access Study interviews
      - 1994 (Box 253, Folder 2-5)
      - 1994 (Box 254-258)
      - 1994 (Box 259, Folder 1)
    - Client Satisfaction focus groups, 1996 (Box 259, Folder 2-3)
    - Client Survey
      - 1993 (Box 259, Folder 4-5)
      - 1993 (Box 260-269)
      - 1993 (Box 270, Folder 1-2)
    - Deaf AIDS Project Brochure focus group, 1995 (Box 270, Folder 3-5)
    - Grief and Healing workshop
      - Preliminary questionnaires
        - 1991-1992 (Box 270, Folder 6)
        - 1991-1992 (Box 271, Folder 1)
      - Volunteer questionnaires
        - 1991-1992 (Box 271, Folder 2-7)
        - 1991-1992 (Box 272, Folder 1)
    - Healthcare questionnaires
      - Undated (Box 272, Folder 2-6)
      - Undated (Box 273, Folder 1-5)
    - HIV Negative Prevention Study questionnaire
      - 1995 (Box 273, Folder 6)
      - 1995 (Box 274-276)
      - 1995 (Box 277, Folder 1-3)
    - Hotline
      - Log sheets, 1997 (Box 277, Folder 4)
      - Questionnaire, 1990 (Box 277, Folder 5-7)
    - Informational Network Study questionnaire
      - 1994 (Box 278-282)
      - 1994 (Box 283, Folder 1-4)
    - Intake survey
      - 1991 (Box 283, Folder 5-6)
      - 1991 (Box 284, Folder 1)
      - 1992-1994 (Box 284, Folder 2-7)
      - Undated (Box 285, Folder 1-5)
    - Intensive Case Management Evaluation questionnaire, 1990 (Box 285, Folder 6)
    - Keep it Up
      - Preliminary questionnaire
        - 1991-1993, n.d. (Box 286-287)
        - Undated (Box 288, Folder 1-4)
      - Follow-up questionnaire
        - 1992 Jan (Box 288, Folder 5)
        - 1992 Mar-Sep (Box 289, Folder 1-6)
        - 1992 Oct-1993, n.d. (Box 290, Folder 1-6)
      - Phone interview
        - 1991 Jun-Jul (Box 290, Folder 7)
        - 1991 Oct-1992 Sep (Box 291, Folder 1-6)
        - 1992 Oct-1993, n.d. (Box 292, Folder 1-4)
    - Living with AIDS TV Show survey
      - 1995-1996 (Box 292, Folder 5-6)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 293, Folder 1-5)
    - Men of Color Discussion Group feedback, 1994-1995 (Box 293, Folder 6)
    - Mental Health Needs assessment
      - 1996 (Box 293, Folder 7)
      - 1996 (Box 294-304)
    - On-site Support Group survey, undated (Box 305, Folder 1)
    - Oral Sex
      - Brochure questionnaire, 1996 (Box 305, Folder 2)
      - Study interviews, 1997 (Box 305, Folder 3-5)
    - Safer Sex interview
      - 1991-1992 Feb (Box 305, Folder 6-7)
      - 1992 Mar-1993, n.d. (Box 306, Folder 1-6)
    - Service Provider interview
      - Secondary Prevention campaign
        - 1992 Mar-Apr (Box 306, Folder 7)
        - 1992 Nov-Dec, n.d. (Box 307, Folder 1-3)
      - Young Adult campaign, 1993 (Box 307, Folder 4)
    - Sex and Alcohol Study interview
      - 1993 (Box 307, Folder 5-6)
      - 1993 (Box 308, Folder 1-5)
      - 1993 (Box 309, Folder 1-4)
    - SUCE Project process notes, 1996-1997 (Box 309, Folder 5-6)
    - Transgender Work Group Staff survey, 1996 (Box 309, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer questionnaires
      - 1990-1993, n.d. (Box 310-314)
      - Undated (Box 315, Folder 1-4)
    - Youth study
      - 1993 (Box 315, Folder 5-6)
      - 1993 (Box 316-318)
      - 1993 (Box 319, Folder 1-3)
  - VIII. C. Topical Files, 1993-1997, n.d.; 1 box
    This subseries contains Topical Files created by members of the Evaluation Department. It consists of procedural documents and research protocol, memoranda, reviews and assorted subject files.
    - Client procedures, undated (Box 319, Folder 4)
    - Coding, 1995, n.d. (Box 319, Folder 5)
    - Concept mapping, 1995 (Box 319, Folder 6)
    - Construction news, 1997 (Box 319, Folder 7)
    - Content analysis of newsletters, 1993-1994 (Box 319, Folder 8)
    - Drugs, 1995-1997 (Box 319, Folder 9)
    - Effectiveness, 1997, n.d. (Box 319, Folder 10)
    - Evaluation manual originals, 1993-1994 (Box 319, Folder 11)
    - Executive Summary Information, 1994 (Box 320, Folder 1)
    - Guatemala, 1996 (Box 320, Folder 2)
    - Health Sciences Information Services, 1997 (Box 320, Folder 3)
    - Housing needs profile, 1995, n.d. (Box 320, Folder 4)
    - Lincoln Hospital acupuncture, 1993 (Box 320, Folder 5)
    - Manual information, 1996 (Box 320, Folder 6)
    - Newborn testing, 1996-1997, n.d. (Box 320, Folder 7)
    - Program review, 1996-1997 (Box 320, Folder 8)
    - SUCE Participant analysis, 1997 (Box 320, Folder 9)
    - Support Center of New York workshop, 1995 (Box 320, Folder 10)
    - Telephone interview guide, undated (Box 320, Folder 11)
    - Women, 1996-1997 (Box 320, Folder 12)
- Series IX. Legal Services Department, 1988, 1991-1995, n.d; 3 folders
  The Legal Services Department provided free legal counseling to clients of GMHC.
  This series contains brochures produced by the Legal Services Department and a manual for volunteer attorneys.
  - Brochures, 1988, 1993-1995, n.d (Box 320, Folder 13)
  - Interest on Lawyer Account Fund of the State of New York, 1995 (Box 320, Folder 14)
  - Volunteer Attorney Procedure Manual, 1988 (Box 320, Folder 15)
- Series X. Office of the Ombudsman, 1975-1978, 1982-1997; 25.5 boxes
  The Office of the Ombudsman was created in 1984 as part of Client Services and became its own department in 1986. The Ombudsman sought to provide advocacy services for PWAs who did not receive satisfactory services through the healthcare and social services systems. The Ombudsman also investigated complaints from within and outside GMHC.
  This series contains correspondence, memoranda, minutes, reports, and other material from the Office of the Ombudsman at GMHC. The series contains three subseries, Administrative Files, Case Files, and Resource Information Files.
  - X. A. Administrative Files, 1982-1991, n.d.; 6.5 boxes
    This subseries contains the Administrative Files of the directors of the Office of the Ombudsman and consists of correspondence, memoranda, reports, and other material regarding the many areas in which PWAs were discriminated against. Included are reports on the funeral industry's reaction to the AIDS crisis, handbooks and briefings on patients' rights, data on other organizations' hotlines, and information on prisoners' rights. The materials in this series were created and utilized by the staff of the Office of the Ombudsman.
    - AIDS and Discrimination in New Jersey, 1988 (Box 320, Folder 16)
    - AIDS Discrimination documentation, 1985-1987 (Box 406, Folder 4)
    - Alternative documentation, 1985-1987 (Box 320, Folder 17)
    - Alternative resources and articles, 1985 (Box 320, Folder 18)
    - Black community and AIDS, 1985-1986 (Box 321, Folder 1)
    - Case histories, 1985-1986 (Box 406, Folder 5)
    - COBRA, 1986-1987 (Box 321, Folder 2)
    - Correctional Association of New York, 1987-1990 (Box 321, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1990s (Box 406, Folder 6)
    - Deaf, 1985-1986 (Box 321, Folder 4)
    - Dermatology, 1986 (Box 321, Folder 5)
    - Discrimination, 1986-1987 (Box 321, Folder 6)
    - Earley, Mark, 1982, 1985-1986 (Box 321, Folder 7)
    - Elisabeth Kubler-Ross Center, 1983-1987 (Box 321, Folder 8-9)
    - Emergency care, 1986 (Box 321, Folder 10)
    - Facility listing, 1980s (Box 321, Folder 11)
    - Famil: A Guide to the Criminal Justice Process for Families of Offenders and Those Who Serve Them, 1986 (Box 321, Folder 12)
    - Fortune Society, 1988 (Box 321, Folder 13)
    - Funeral home industry, 1985-1987 (Box 321, Folder 14)
    - GMHC Policy Statement on Court Ordered HIV Antibody Testing of Criminal Defendants, 1990 (Box 322, Folder 1)
    - Haitians, 1980s (Box 322, Folder 2)
    - Handicapped, 1984 (Box 322, Folder 3)
    - Health Systems Agency of New York City, 1983-1987 (Box 322, Folder 4)
    - HIP patient information, 1986-1987 (Box 322, Folder 5)
    - Hispanic AIDS Forum, 1980s (Box 322, Folder 6)
    - Historical files, 1985, 1988 (Box 322, Folder 7)
    - HIV in prison, 1989 (Box 322, Folder 8)
    - Hospices
      - General, 1987 (Box 322, Folder 9)
      - Information, 1983-1985 (Box 322, Folder 10)
      - Resources, 1983-1987 (Box 322, Folder 11)
    - Hospitals
      - Contacts, 1983-1985 (Box 322, Folder 12)
      - Information and resources, 1986-1987 (Box 322, Folder 13)
      - Patients' rights, 1988-1989 (Box 323, Folder 1)
    - Hotlines, 1983-1987 (Box 323, Folder 2-3)
    - Housing, 1985-1986 (Box 323, Folder 4)
    - HTLV-III, 1985-1986 (Box 323, Folder 5)
    - Human Rights Campaign Fund, 1985-1987 (Box 323, Folder 6)
    - Identity House, 1984 (Box 323, Folder 7)
    - Infusion case file, 1989-1990 (Box 323, Folder 8)
    - Insurance, 1985-1989 (Box 323, Folder 9-11)
    - Intravenous drug users, 1985-1986, 1990 (Box 324, Folder 1-2)
    - Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals: Health Care Advocacy for the Patient with AIDS, 1986 (Box 324, Folder 3)
    - Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund AIDS Legal Guide, 1984 (Box 324, Folder 4)
    - Lawsuits, 1989 (Box 324, Folder 5)
    - Legal
      - General, 1984-1987 (Box 324, Folder 6-8)
      - Attorney's Manual and Legal Services Program, 1985 (Box 324, Folder 9)
    - Legislation, 1988-1990 (Box 325, Folder 1)
    - Lesbian and Gay Community Center, 1985-1988 (Box 325, Folder 2)
    - Lesbians/Women, 1982-1985 (Box 325, Folder 3)
    - Medicaid
      - Food supplements, 1989 (Box 325, Folder 4)
      - Growth of the AIDS Epidemic in Medicaid, 1987 (Box 325, Folder 5)
      - Medicare, 1986-1990 (Box 325, Folder 6)
      - Public Education Training Manual for the Professional Health and Social Service Community, 1987 (Box 325, Folder 7)
      - Utilization threshold system, 1989-1990 (Box 325, Folder 8)
    - Midpoint Service Inc., 1980s (Box 325, Folder 9)